What's up everyone? Today we're going to be going over a foundational understanding of your business.
It's going to be for entrepreneurs, aspiring business owners, already existing business owners.
We will be going over from the idea to income, so to speak.
I'm going to go over first in module zero a little bit more about myself.
I come from a background of data science and marketing, and I want you to understand exactly why that's an important aspect for your business.
Specifically, I had worked with a company called Kantar.
It held market research surveys for different businesses across all socials, across digital, across billboards, across any type of advertising.
We would help measure that for businesses, run analytic research surveys, and then deliver how different campaigns went, future predictions, and how to better advertise either a specific product or their business as a whole.
I moved on to specifically a company called Samba TV, where they have more TV measurement analytics.
So both the background in CTV, any of the linear TV, or any of the streaming services, if you are interested in running advertising on those,
if you are even ready to start advertising on those platforms, I have plenty of experience on that.
Moving forward with the module, from idea to income.
Whether you're already making money, whether you haven't really figured out what your service or product is going to be,
this is really important because if I'm trying to, or Terramor, right, our marketing consulting company,
is going to try and help move the needle in sales, it really needs to have sub-goals below that.
You can't just say, this month, we killed it in sales, you want to understand why.
This month, we failed in sales, we are firing everyone, right?
You want to understand why.
And this is the foundation for understanding the why behind that.
So like I had said, who this is for, this is for side hustlers, this is for seeking your first clients.
You will need to do some warm outreach for this course.
It's definitely important to move along the way.
By that, I mean, don't just take this course, finish it, and then say,
all right, time for me to do things.
Do things along the way, super important.
Outcome for your first dollar, you're not looking for some super difficult service
that will only help one customer.
You want a repeatable system to implement, so it can just be off the shelf.
Whether that's a service or a product, you want it to be run many a times, right?
Whether that's a low price point or a high-end price point, it needs to be repeatable.
Going over the course agenda, take a look at this.
I'm not going to say it out loud.
And then, like I had mentioned, how to use this course, right?
Watch one lesson as quickly or as slowly as you need.
Do the worksheets.
Send five messages a day.
That is that warm outreach that we had talked about.
And we're going to go over some of the tools that we use here at Terramore.io,
as well as what we help implement for different businesses.
So the ones we use, the ones you can use, free, freemium, paid.
We'll go over all of them.
And then, we'll go over all of them.
Bak, what we need to explain.
Okay.
Well, if you choose from the left America, we'll go over all of them.
You're the one that won't go over all of them.